{
    "data": [
        {
            "answer": "A) Laxman and Shatrughan\nB) Ram\nC) Laxman\nD) All four brothers",
            "question": "Q1.Which son was most loved by Sumitra?"
        },
        {
            "answer": "A) Humayun\nB) Akbar\nC) Jahangir\nD) Shahjahan",
            "question": "Q2.Who built the famous Shalimar bagh of Srinagar?"
        },
        {
            "answer": "A) Facebook\nB) Twitter\nC) Google Plus\nD) Tagged",
            "question": "Q3.Which social networking site was used by government to invite suggestions from citizens for recently conducted budget?"
        },
        {
            "answer": "A) Labrador Sea\u200e\nB) James Bay\u200e\nC) The English Channel\nD) Greenland Sea",
            "question": "Q4.What runs between the North Sea and the Atlantic Ocean?"
        },
        {
            "answer": "A) Deccan Chargers\nB) Chennai Super Kings\nC) Kolkata Knight Riders\nD) Delhi Daredevils",
            "question": "Q5.Which team won the IPL (2009)?"
        },
        {
            "answer": "A) 1992\nB) 1995\nC) 1996\nD) 1994",
            "question": "Q6.In which year's budget government introduced Service Tax?"
        },
        {
            "answer": "A) Buddhist and Jain\nB) Hindu and Muslim\nC) Buddhist only\nD) Hindu, Buddhist and Jain",
            "question": "Q7.The caves and rock-cut temples at Ellora are?"
        },
        {
            "answer": "A) GDB ( human)\nB) SWISS - PROT\nC) Protein 3D structure\nD) Gene bank protein",
            "question": "Q8.Which one of the following is not a primary Database?"
        },
        {
            "answer": "A) Allaudin Khilji\nB) Babur\nC) Ibrahim Lodi\nD) Shahjahan",
            "question": "Q9.Who among the following built the famous Alai Darwaza?"
        },
        {
            "answer": "A) Gift Tax\nB) Wealth tax\nC) Education Tax\nD) Road tax",
            "question": "Q10.Which tax was abolished by government in 2015 Budget?"
        }
    ]
}